Railway Labor Executives' Association Records 5484
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IV: Office Files, 1961
  - Legislation: National Advisory Committee on Rail Transportation, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Car and Track Inspection Bill, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Highway Financing, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Repeal of Taxes on Transportation, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: National Transportation Policy [folder 1 of 2], 1961 (Box 88, Folder 6a)
  - Legislation: National Transportation Policy [folder 2 of 2], 1961 (Box 88, Folder 6b)
  - Legislation: Railroad Retirement Act [folder 1 of 2], 1961 (Box 88, Folder 7a)
  - Legislation: Railroad Retirement Act [folder 2 of 2], 1961 (Box 88, Folder 7b)
  - Legislation: Bills to Amend the Railroad Retirement Act, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: S. 1732 and HR 7377, "Super-Grades", Amendment to Railroad Retirement Act, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Bills to Amend the Railroad Retirement Act, HR 8597 and S. 2395, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Railroad Unemployment Insurance Act, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: Unemployment Situation, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Labor-Management Relations Act, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Social Security Act, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: Medical Benefits to Retired People [folder 1 of 3], 1961 (Box 88, Folder 15a)
  - Legislation: Medical Benefits to Retired People [folder 2 of 3], 1961 (Box 88, Folder 15b)
  - Legislation: Medical Benefits to Retired People [folder 3 of 3], 1961 (Box 88, Folder 15c)
  - Legislation: Mail, Parcel Post, and Express, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: State Legislation, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: Full Crew Laws, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: Right to Work Laws, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: State Public Utilities Commissions, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: National Labor Relations Act, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: Mass Transportation, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Legislative, Bills Pertaining to Federal Employees and Veterans, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - Legislation: Waterways, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - Legislation: Anti-Labor Legislation, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Legislation: Depressed Areas, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Legislation: Minimum Wage Legislation, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - Legislation: Hours of Service Law Violations, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - RLEA: General, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 29)
  - RLEA: Constitution and By-Laws, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 30)
  - RLEA: Officers and Members, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 31)
  - RLEA: Canadian Affairs, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - RLEA Meetings, General, 1961 (Box 88, Folder 33)
  - Legislation: To Amend Norris-LaGuardia Act, MLRA and RLA, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Railway Labor Act, General, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Interstate Commerce Act, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Interstate Commerce Act, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    `
  - RLEA: Agendas, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - RLEA: Reports of Counsel, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - RLEA: Assessments, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - RLEA: Applications for Affiliation, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - RLEA: Wages and Rules, General, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - RLEA: Southern Rules Movement, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - RLEA: Chicago and North Western Rules Movement, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - RLEA: Butte, Anaconda, and Pacific Rules Movement, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - RLEA: Job Stabilization Movement on MKT Railroad, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - RLEA: 1961 Wage and Rules Movement (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - RLEA: Radio-Telephone Communications, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - RLEA: Health and Welfare, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - RLEA: Travelers Insurance Coverage, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - RLEA: Non-Operating Unions, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - RLEA: Operating Unions, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - RLEA: Rules Committee, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - RLEA: Carrier Strike Insurance Program, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - RLEA: Automation, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - RLEA: Union Shop, General, 1961 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - RLEA: Diversification of Railroads, "Piggybacking," etc., 1961 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - RLEA: Permits on Railroad Property for Union Business, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - RLEA: Washington Job Protection Agreement (WJPA) - General, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    Property Revisions, railroads, and unions parties thereto.
  - RLEA: WJPA, Section 13 Committee, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - RLEA: Railway Labor Building, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - RLEA: Committees, General, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - RLEA: Train Accidents, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - RLEA: Safety Committee, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - RLEA: Public Relations, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - RLEA: Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Consolidations, etc., File 2, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - RLEA: Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Consolidations, etc., File 1 [folder 1 of 2], 1961 (Box 90, Folder 11a)
  - RLEA: Committee to Study Railroad Mergers, Consolidations, Etc. File 1 [folder 2 of 2], 1961 (Box 90, Folder 11b)
  - RLEA: Keyserling Merger Study, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - RLEA: Committee to Meet with AAR, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - RLEA: Legislative Representatives, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - RLEA: Passes, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - RLEA: Prospective Employees, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - RLEA: Personnel Records, General, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - RLEA: Financial, General, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - RLEA: Financial, Statements, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - RLEA: Workmen's Compensation, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - RLEA: Traveler's Insurance Company, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - RLEA: GPO Account No. 11256, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - RLEA: Insurance, General, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - RLEA: Postage Meter, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - RLEA: Addressograph-Multilith, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - RLEA: Office Equipment, General, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - RLEA: Thermo-Fax Comply Machine, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - RLEA: Office Furniture, General, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - RLEA: Lobbying, Registration for, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - RLEA: Lawyers, General, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, General, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Other Organizations: News from the AFL-CIO, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Other Organizations: Collective Bargaining Report, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 33)
  - Other Organizations: COPE, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - Other Organizations: Free Trade Union News, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 35)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO Minutes, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 36)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, National Legislative Council - Minutes, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 37)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Legislative Action Bulletin, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 38)
  - Other Organizations: AFL-CIO, Legislative Council, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 39)
  - Other Organizations: Miscellaneous Organizations, general, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - Other Organizations: Advertising Council, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 41)
  - Other Organizations: National Safety Council, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 42)
  - Other Organizations: Pension Associations, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 43)
  - Other Organizations: Young Men's Christian Association, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 44)
  - Other Organizations: Committee for a National Trade Policy, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 45)
  - Other Organizations: Harvard University, Trade Union Program, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 46)
  - Other Organizations: The Unions Retirement Foundation, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 47)
  - Other Organizations: US Committee for United Nations, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 48)
  - Other Organizations: National, Conference on International Economic and Social Development, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 49)
  - Other Organizations: Charities, General, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 50)
  - Other Organizations: American Cancer Society, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 51)
  - Other Organizations: American Red Cross, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 52)
  - Other Organizations: Railway Labor's Political League, General, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 53)
  - Other Organizations: National Association of Retired and Veteran Railway Employees, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 54)
  - Other Organizations: Dual Organizations, General, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 55)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Bureau of Middle West, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 56)
  - Other Organizations: Labor Newspaper, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 57)
  - International Affairs: General, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - International Affairs: Second Half, Officer of International Labor Affairs (File 1), 1961 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - International Affairs: Second Half, Office of International Labor Affairs (File 2), 1961 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - International Affairs: First Half, Office of International Labor Affairs [folder 1 of 2], 1961 (Box 91, Folder 4a)
  - International Affairs: First Half, Office of International Labor Affairs [folder 2 of 2], 1961 (Box 91, Folder 4b)
  - International Affairs: Team Managers, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - International Affairs: Trade Union Advisory Committee, Department of Labor, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - International Affairs: Joint US-Mexico Trade Union Committee, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - International Affairs: International Labor Office (ILO), 1961 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - International Affairs: News from the ILO, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - International Affairs: international Confederation of Free Trade Unions, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - International Affairs: Press Release, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - International Affairs: News, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - International Affairs: Radio Service, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - International Affairs: Spotlight, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - International Affairs: Press Communique, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - International Affairs: Information Bulletins, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers' Federation [folder 1 of 2], 1961 (Box 91, Folder 17a)
  - International Affairs: International Transport Workers' Federation [folder 2 of 2], 1961 (Box 91, Folder 17b)
  - International Affairs: ITF Affiliation Fees, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - International Affairs: ITF Circulars, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - International Affairs: ITF Press Reports, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - International Affairs: ITF Minutes, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - International Affairs: ITF Congress, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - International Affairs: ITF Executive Committee, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - International Affairs: ITF Management Committee, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - International Affairs: International Cooperation Administration (ICA), 1961 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - International Affairs: Postal Telegraph and Telephone International, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - International Affairs: Regional Activities, General, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - International Affairs: Latin American Affairs (Azana), 1961 (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - International Affairs: Latin American Affairs (Otero), 1961 (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - International Affairs: African Affairs (ITF) (LaFlamme), 1961 (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - International Affairs: Asian Affairs (ITF and ICFTU) (Soares), 1961 (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - International Affairs: International Labor Training Program, General (ITF), 1961 (Box 91, Folder 32)
  - International Affairs: Robert H. Aiken, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 33)
  - International Affairs: Thomas R. Crabtree, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 34)
  - International Affairs: Walter Townsend, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 35)
  - Government: International Labour Organization, Inland Transport Committee - Note on the Proceedings of the Seventh Session, 1961 (Box 157, Folder 14)
    Geneva, May 8-19, 1961
  - Government: ILO, Inland Transport Committee - General Report, First Item on the Agenda, 1961 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    Legislation: Seventh Session, Geneva. Bound.
  - Government: ILO, Inland Transport Committee - General Report, Second Item on the Agenda, 1961 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    Seventh Session, Geneva. Bound.
  - Government: ILO, Inland Transport Committee - General Report, Third Item on the Agenda, 1961 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Commuter Problems: Philadelphia Service Inspection Corporation [folder 1 of 3], 1961 (Box 91, Folder 36a)
  - Commuter Problems: Philadelphia Service Inspection Corporation [folder 2 of 3], 1961 (Box 91, Folder 36b)
  - Commuter Problems: Philadelphia Service Inspection Corporation [folder 3 of 3], 1961 (Box 91, Folder 36c)
  - Commuter Problems: General, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 37)
  - Commuter Problems: New Haven Fares [folder 1 of 4], 1961 (Box 92, Folder 1a)
  - Commuter Problems: New Haven Fares [folder 2 of 4], 1961 (Box 92, Folder 1b)
  - Commuter Problems: New Haven Fares [folder 3 of 4], 1961 (Box 92, Folder 1c)
  - Commuter Problems: New Haven Fares [folder 4 of 4], 1961 (Box 92, Folder 1d)
  - RLEA: Bills [folder 1 of 2], 1961 (Box 92, Folder 2a)
  - RLEA: Bills [folder 2 of 2], 1961 (Box 92, Folder 2b)
  - RLEA: Strikes, General, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - RLEA: Railroads, General, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Railroads: Association of American Railroads, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Railroads: Association of Western Railways, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Railroads: Carriers' Conference Committees, General, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Railroads: Hospital Associations, General, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Railroads: Eastern Governors Conference on Railroad Problems, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Railroads: KCS, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Railroads: Missouri Pacific, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Railroads: Illinois Central, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 12)
- Series V: Office Files, 1962
  This series consists of the Office Files of the RLEA for the year 1962. They are arranged into seven record groups: Government, Legislation, RLEA, Railroads, Other Organizations, International Affairs, and Commuter Problems.
  - Government: Constitution, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Government: Executive Branch, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Government: House and Senate, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Government: NY Candidacy for Senate, JB Donovan, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Government: Judicial branch, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Government: US National Committee, Pan American Congress Association, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Government: State Department, General, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Government: Summary of Activities [folder 1 of 2], 1962 (Box 93, Folder 8a)
  - Government: Summary of Activities [folder 2 of 2], 1962 (Box 93, Folder 8b)
  - Government: Treasury Department, General, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Government: Payroll Savings Division, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Government: Internal Revenue Service, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Government: Defense Department, General, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Government: Office of Emergency Planning (OCDM), 1962 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Government: Labor-Management Manpower Policy Committee, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Government: Regional Manpower Committee, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Government: Commerce Department, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Government: Labor Department, General, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - Government: Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS), 1962 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Government: BLS, Wage Chronology no. 40, Non-Operating Employees, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Government: Bureau of Labor Standards, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - Government: Bureau of Labor-Management Reports, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - Government: Interstate Commerce Commission, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - Government: ICC Membership and Staff Appointments, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - Government: ICC Rules and Administrative Procedures, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 25)
  - Government: ICC M400, Summary of Accidents, Etc., 1962 (Box 93, Folder 26)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, Accident Reports, Form "I", 1962 (Box 93, Folder 27)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, Carriers' Monthly Hours of Service Report, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 28)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, M211 Freight Train Performance, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 29)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, 230, Fuel and Power for Locomotives, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 30)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, 240, Motive Power and Car Equipment, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 31)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, 200, Operating Statistics of Steam Railways, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 32)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, 100-150, Operating Revenues and Expenses, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 33)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, 250, Passenger traffic, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 34)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, 213, Passenger Train Performance, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 35)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, 200, Revenue Traffic, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 36)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, 125, Selected Income and Balance Sheets, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 37)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, 215, Yard Service and Performance, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 38)
  - Government: ICC Statistics, Steam Railways, Class I Wages Monthly, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 39)
  - Government: ICC M300, Changes in Reporting Requirements from Monthly to Quarterly, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 40)
  - Government: ICC Accounting Rules, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 41)
  - Government: ICC Rules for Reporting Accidents, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 42)
  - Government: ICC Report Forms for Reporting Accidents, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 43)
  - Government: ICC Designation of Persons to Examine Accident Reports, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 44)
  - Government: ICC Accident Reports, Miscellaneous [folder 1 of 2], 1962 (Box 93, Folder 45a)
  - Government: Accident reports, Miscellaneous [folder 2 of 2], 1962 (Box 93, Folder 45b)
  - Government: Existing Track and Signal Layout, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 46)
  - Government: Rules, Standards, and Instructions re: Signal Systems [folder 1 of 2], 1962 (Box 93, Folder 47a)
  - Government: Rules, Standards, and Instructions re: Signal Systems [folder 2 of 2], 1962 (Box 93, Folder 47b)
  - Government: RS and I Cases, Approval of Changes in Signal Installations, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Government: RS and I Cases, Approval of Changes in Signal Installations, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Government: RS and I Cases, Approval of Changes in Signal Installations, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Government: RS and I Cases, Approval of Changes in Signal Installations, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Government: Bureau of Transport Economics and Statistics, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Government: Rules for Reporting of Wages and Hours, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Government: Bureau of Safety and Service, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Government: Complaints re: Administration of Safety Laws and Regulations, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Government: Bureau of Locomotive Inspection, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Government: Power Brakes, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Government: ICC Safety Dockets, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Government: Union Tank Car Company, #32258, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Government: Application of Safety Appliance Act to track MotorCars, #32248, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Government: Prevention of Rail-Highway Accidents, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Government: Less than Carload Discontinuances, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Government: Less Than Carload Discontinuances [folder 1 of 2], 1962 (Box 94, Folder 16a)
  - Government: Less Than Carload Discontinuances [folder 2 of 2], 1962 (Box 94, Folder 16b)
  - Government: Less Than Carload Discontinuances (1st Quarter) [folder 1 of 2], 1962 (Box 94, Folder 17a)
  - Government: Less Than Carload Discontinuances (1st Quarter) [folder 2 of 2], 1962 (Box 94, Folder 17b)
  - Government: Motor Carriers, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Government: Gulf Transport Company, Application, MC-86761, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Government: NYC, Application, MC-67916, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Government: Less Than Carload Discontinuances [folder 1 of 2], 1962 (Box 94, Folder 21a)
  - Government: Less Than Carload Discontinuances [folder 2 of 2], 1962 (Box 94, Folder 21b)
  - Government: Less Than Carload Discontinuances (Close Cases), 1962 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Membership and Staff Appointment, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Rules of Procedure and Administrative Practice, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Appropriations, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Lists of Carriers and Designated Officers to Handle Disputes, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Monthly Reports on Status of Cases, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Decisions and Certifications, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, Flight Engineers' Representation, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Government: National Mediation Board, C and NW and 14 Cooperative Organizations Case, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Government: National Railroad Adjustment Board (NRAB), 1962 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Government: NRAB, First Division, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Government: NRAB, Second Division, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Government: NRAB, Third Division, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Government: NRAB, Fourth Division, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Government: NRAB, Organizations, Qualified to Participate in Selection of Members, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Government: NRAB, Membership, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Government: NRAB, Application of Awards, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Government: NRAB, Thirds Party Notices, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Supplementary Material Relating to the Board's Activities Distributed by Labor Member at Meetings [folder 1 of 2], 1962 (Box 95, Folder 20a)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Supplementary Material Relating to the Board's Activities Distributed by Labor Member at Meetings [folder 2 of 2], 1962 (Box 95, Folder 20b)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Membership and Staff Appointments, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Field Offices, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Mechanizations and centralizations of Payments, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Coverage of Railroads and Unions as Employers, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Status of Funds, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Presidential Railroad Communications, Impact on Railroad Retirement and Unemployment Insurance Systems, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Military Service Credits, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Educational Programs, Meetings, Films, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Press Releases, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Supplemental Pension Plans, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, Safety Studies, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Government: Railroad Retirement Board, National Reporting Officers Memoranda, General, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - Government: President's Committee on Physically Handicapped, 1961-1962 (Box 95, Folder 33)
  - Government: President's Communication on Equal Employment Opportunities, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 34)
  - Government: Peace Corps, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 35)
  - Government: President's Commission on the Status of Women, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 36)
  - Government: Freedom from Hunger Foundation, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 37)
  - Judicial: Court Cases, General, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 38)